London the capital of the United Kingdom often called Northern Ireland and mates
But it was once the capital of the entire world and it still has those
Capital of the entire world prices spent 30 pounds on breakfast once like a dumbass, but now you won't have to. Hello
I'm Killian, and I'm here to save you a plane ticket.
Two weeks ago I decided to fly to London with two goals
visit and review every tourist attraction and
Find Jack the Ripper. It's been 130 years. It's time to bring in a professional when I landed on Friday. It was sunny, London
It's not supposed to be sunny supposed to be foggy and cloudy. I was worried weather would ruin my trip
Fortunately for the rest of my visit the weather was properly depressing
So what attraction should I start with? Maybe the oldest one. The Tower of London. Yes
Your first thought is that is not a Tower
That's a fort and next to the fort is The Tower Bridge, which actually has two towers and the city itself is called Lunden
But it has two O's in it so it should be called low and down this rabbit hole never ends
Just stay out of it
the Tower's been a Palace, a fort, a
Prison and the top rated TripAdvisor page many visit for this building which houses the crown jewels. They are
Protected by a very long queue to bore thieves into not stealing
I preferred the old crown jewels in this house. Can... can someone steal them for me?
I think you can climb on this as Assassin´s Creed style and then sort of mission
Impossible your way in and if you then mail them to me, I will PayPal you 200 bucks. The building in the middle is called the white
Brown-ish tower. It's a weapons museum where you can find cannons and
medieval
Assault rifles it even has weapons used in actual battles like this
robot dragon used against a French Robot Unicorn
But when I walk around this fort, I can't shake the feeling that it was better back in the day
There used to be a polar bear and animal gladiator fights
Vegetarians really ruin the appeal of this place worse than that
The tower guards are called beefeaters because they were paid in beef now
They are allegedly paid in money, which makes this whole place unauthentic
The cafeteria doesn't even serve roast beef turn it back into a prison
Let's go to the neighbor attraction instead Tower Bridge finished in
1894 its purpose was to be in the background of social media photos so that you can show people you went to London they had
To close down the top portion in 1910 because like everything if you leave it alone long enough
it becomes a brothel so you have to realize that my
expectations were impossibly high
But they turn it into a place to read bridge facts barely any prostitutes. Then you go to the engine room
I like steampunk
So this place is pretty neat
But tickets were 7 pounds and they didn't let us open the bridge we pay we say from the bridge you can see st
Paul's Cathedral and people, this is one mighty building but scam warning not actually owned by st
Paul it was tallest building in the city for 300 years until they built this thing
Surpassing it in both height and beauty beautiful art a great view from the roof
But the most important thing of all probably has the best museum coffee, but the decorations kind of hurt my enjoyment
I'm looking at the statue raised to a general that fell to the French at Waterloo and I feel kinda guilty
Sitting here eating a croissant
Those are three famous London buildings, but let's visit the most famous one of them all Palace of Westminster
It's so fun being in another country's parliament because it's like here decisions are made
That doesn't affect me at all
Look its battle paintings listen to an audio guide fail to convince you the Queen shouldn't have all the power
But I really came here to find out if Jack the Ripper was a government cover-up
So I asked the Prime Minister, but it was awkward because she was trying to get through a door
But was holding two Starbucks cups, but refused to put one down and refused to ask me for help
She said there are no classified documents in the Elizabeth Tower. So I
Can't get in there because it's cocooning to become a butterfly
I do agree that it's a bit suspicious that they randomly decided to renovate it
Just two years before I came here
You might have heard this tower called by another name
But that's actually the Bell and if you call it Big Ben the locals, they will have no idea what you're talking about
We just confuse them. So I learned nothing about Jack and as a side effect. I learned the entire history of London
so now I might as well share it with you The history of London, so
at some point in history
They created London then it gained enough experience
To become Victorian London and they built a clock and it made a bunch of money so they said to themselves
How can we make more tourist money find out in the next segment Killian visits tourist traps! This is a Travel Guide
So I have to do things. I don't want to do for example visit Coca-Cola presents the Coca-Cola London Eye
By Coca-Cola a big ferris wheel sponsored by an American soft drink company
Can't remember which one it is the slow ferries, right? It can't be that bad wrong
It was raining trying to book the correct ticket might require in eBook
They tried to get me to buy 50 add-ons while standing in line a large school class appeared in front of me
I'm guessing from another dimension a woman was complaining to an employee about the weather as it is
Sixteen-year-old intern had the power to change the will of God and I had to pee I just wanted to go see the fishies
I recommend London Eye to everyone protip to the food trucks next to the eye
You can make a fortune selling Pepsi from all the people taking ironic pictures
I guess you still make money from the huge crowds, but I want to visit the most overcrowded attraction in London backs people
I think the line to get in was 30 minutes and the line to buy tickets were two hours
If only some local lads had connected all the computers so you could buy a ticket from one of those
You were obviously not supposed to visit this place alone
The entrance code actually said oh you're alone you were supposed to go with someone and say wow
some of these look really realistic and some of these don't
And they will agree with you and you will live happily ever after there's also a ride that shows the history of London
But what's the point now that you have this video? I like these Story characters
But last time I was here camera phones were not mainstream and my god can't I go to another place filled with
pop-culture references and royal wedding souvenirs like
Westminster Abbey, it's the burial site of
3,300 people
Composers writers scientists Queens Kings. No one above that though I'm saying there are no footballers
everyone has a monument and expect the grandest monuments to belong to someone important but it's usually like the Duke of Arsenal's cat's
Previous owner. It's been the coronation site of every British King
I don't know the rules I snuck in and sat on the coronation chair and coordinated myself
I think I'm the king of Britain now. If not, I'm very disappointed
Mister edsall building. I can look out over my kingdom a building that looks like your mother
Wanted to make your apartment less depressing so she bought a generic vase
What's that the view from the shard is surprisingly nice go to the 68th floor
Grab some champagne and realize you didn't actually have to visit all these landmarks. You could've just enjoyed them from here
God save you London computer speaker or London air conditioner. What do people call you the
Walkie-talkie. It looks nothing like one, but that makes sense
See during the tower this beautiful baby needs protection and the best way to protect him is the HMS Belfast
You walk around this light cruiser turned museum and you think to yourself
how could they live like this then you find out they drank rum literally every day and you're like, oh
Do they have any openings? I mean sure everything looks cramped and uncomfortable, but god damn
Did they have some nice toilets?
Honestly, though same problem like with the bridge even though they have a bunch of missiles fact
they don't let you fire the cannons the disappointment in the
Seven-year-old girls faces makes this museum so hard to bear but it reminds me that
Vacations are supposed to be relaxing but this is a Travel Guide. I have walked non-stop
I've basically been on a military march every day much will visit the Imperial War Museum
That shows Britain in World War one, two and cold war. Conditions
Of the soldiers during World War one were really terrible
I can relate after my visit to the Eye museum also runs
Churchill's bunker a man who insulted so many people they decided he should insult a guy named
Adolf into defeat. the World War 1 excavation is very ambitious World War two less so
I think it's to show how unprepared Britain was for the Second World War by being less prepared for visitors
Both of these places threw me out because I was the last one left his entire city closes too early yet
Seeing these memories of divide
Reminds me why I created this new series
To flex on you bitches while you'll be sitting at home
I'll be flying in the premium rest of economy sleeping in the freshest four-star hotels and eating at the fanciest
Fast-food places but doing that has made me broke
Today's sponsor the third reason I went to England to hide my identity online
Then I found out I could have just used North VPN
They have over 1,000 servers in 61 plus countries including this place
Click the link in the top of the description for 75% of a three-year plan
And if you use the code Killian experience you get a month for free. So why do I need internet privacy?
It's because I like pineapple on pizza. There are ancient orders trying to hunt us down
If a VPN had single data encryption
They might find us but Nord VPN has double data encryption for increased anonymity
Click on top link in the description Nord VPN now sponsoring a nord. Now that I have zero money
I need to check out free stuff. So we are off to a Plaza called
Trafalgar Square, it celebrates Admiral Nelson who single-handedly
Bet I am the first person to make that pun. Defeated Napoleon's Navy
Behind the square is a building containing paintings if you weren't sure what paintings are
It's like concept art for history it even has an entire room dedicated to the smartest ninja turtle
Even if it's full of epic artwork, this one is my favorite
It's doctors debating Jesus, but he already knows everything like me
I like it because the doctors like who is this guy and Jesus breaks the fourth wall and looks at the audience like
They don't even know. I'm the Son of God, not every painting is great
Some of these are obviously as to word clipart
But I can't show you most of these paintings because I'll get demonetised then I got ripped off again
I went to a British Museum, but it was a world history museum you go through a timeline of ancient artifact
So it's like Egyptian stuff then Assyrian then Greek Persian
Roman and that's as far as I got before they closed it maybe the next
Country's like Texas, an ancient barbecue
I love this place because of the audio guide a British narrator can form a completely different picture of history
they are like the centaur part represent the powerful bites of Athens democracy when in reality
it was just some drunk Greek aristocrat going Hey!
Make one of the worst people bites the guy this place is massive all these giant
Imperial buildings how huge must my new house be make your way through a bunch of commercials to reach
Buckingham Palace. Oh
I'm sorry, it's not that impressive when Parliament is done discussing their current problem in
2050 they should really consider giving the Queen the gherkin gherkin ham palace
All right. I don't want to be king anymore. I'm going home with it being Sunday
It was time to return to Sweden where it's 15 degrees colder worst country
So that was my weekend in London. God, dammit
I forgot to catch Jack the Ripper what I'm saying all attractions have major flaws and Reaper is still on the loose
So if you're ever in London just stay in your hotel room and only order room service and that's the kilian experience